{
    "subject": "resource/56th_Infantry_Division_(German_Empire)",
    "predicate": "ontology/battle",
    "object": "resource/Battle_of_Verdun",
    "human_readable": "The 56th Infantry Division (German Empire) fought in the Battle of Verdun.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9743837714195251,
            "question": "Was the 56th Infantry Division successful in the Battle of Verdun?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9544768929481506,
            "question": "Which battle did the 56th Infantry Division (German Empire) participate in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7899964451789856,
            "question": "What country was the 56th Infantry Division part of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6826410293579102,
            "question": "Where did the Battle of Verdun occur?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6807696223258972,
            "question": "What type of military unit was the 56th Infantry Division?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5707352161407471,
            "question": "In what century did the Battle of Verdun take place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4923815429210663,
            "question": "Who were some key military leaders involved in the Battle of Verdun?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3794437050819397,
            "question": "What were the main objectives of the Battle of Verdun for each side involved?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28797975182533264,
            "question": "Were there any significant losses on either side during the Battle of Verdun?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2871151268482208,
            "question": "How long did the Battle of Verdun last?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The 56th Infantry Division (German Empire) fought in the Battle of Verdun.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2081_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any significant losses on either side during the Battle of Verdun?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2081_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were the main objectives of the Battle of Verdun for each side involved?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2081_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who were some key military leaders involved in the Battle of Verdun?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2081_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2081_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2081_122.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2081_131.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2081_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2081_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2081_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2081_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2081_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2081_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2081_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that the 56th Infantry Division participated in various battles, including the Battle of Verdun. Therefore, the information supports the statement that the 56th Infantry Division (German Empire) fought in the Battle of Verdun."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}